Narrator: 13
Speaker: buy a pizza
Narrator: 9
Speaker: call a taxi
Narrator: 1
Speaker: dance the tango
Narrator: 11
Speaker: draw a picture
Narrator: 2
Speaker: find a parking space
Narrator: 6
Speaker: forget somebody’s name
Narrator: 21
Speaker: give somebody flowers
Narrator: 19
Speaker: hear a noise
Narrator: 8
Speaker: help somebody
Narrator: 3
Speaker: leave your bag on a train
Narrator: 22
Speaker: look for your keys
Narrator: 18
Speaker: meet a friend
Narrator: 15
Speaker: paint a picture
Narrator: 5
Speaker: remember somebody’s name
Narrator: 17
Speaker: run a race
Narrator: 7
Speaker: see a film
Narrator: 24
Speaker: send a message
Narrator: 12
Speaker: sing a song
Narrator: 25
Speaker: swim in the sea
Narrator: 16
Speaker: take a photo
Narrator: 10
Speaker: talk to a friend
Narrator: 14
Speaker: tell somebody a secret
Narrator: 20
Speaker: try to open a door
Narrator: 23
Speaker: use an app
Narrator: 4
Speaker: wait for a bus